（前情回顾）
这位就是露比？
So this is Ruby, huh?
萨姆 她可是个魔鬼
She's a demon, Sam.
她叫莉莉丝
Her name is Lilith.
她看你不太顺眼
She doesn't like you very much.
你还剩多久？
How long did they give you?
一年
One year.
你早就知晓迪恩和魔鬼做交易的事吗
Did you know about dean's deal?
- 还有莉莉丝是他契约的持有人？- 我知道
- That lilith holds the contract? - Yes.
只剩两个月时间 迪恩 你不会丢下我去地狱的
You got two months left, dean.you're not gonna go to hell.
它不是露比 是莉莉丝
It's not ruby.it's lilith!
露比哪去了
Where's ruby?
我把她赶的远远的了
I sent her far, far away.
小乖乖们 上吧
Sic him, boy.
救救我啊
Somebody help me!
萨姆
Sam!
救命
Help!
[邪恶力量 第4季第1集]
有人吗
Hello?
9月…
September…
很抱歉
We're sorry.
您所拨打的电话无法接通
You have reached a number that has been disconnected.
找谁
Yeah?
- 鲍比吗 - 是的
- Bobby? - Yeah.
- 是我的 - 你是谁
- It's me. - Who's "me"?
迪恩啊
Dean.
你究竟是谁
Who is this?
鲍比 听我说
Bobby, listen to me.
这不好玩 你再打来我就毙了你
This ain't funny. Call again and I'll kill you.
惊讶吧
Surprise.
我不…
I don't…
对的 我也不相信
Yeah, me neither.
但事实如此
But here I am.
鲍比
Bobby!
鲍比 是我啊
Bobby, it's me!
鬼才信你
My ass.
慢着 慢着 慢着
Whoa, whoa, whoa!wait!
你的全名是罗伯特 斯蒂文 辛格
Your name is robert steven singer.
你成为猎鬼者是因为你太太被魔鬼附身
You became a hunter after your wife got possessed.
你和我情如父子
You're about the closest thing I have to a father.
鲍比 真的是我
Bobby…it's me.
我不是变形人
I am not a shapeshifter.
那就是复仇幽灵了
Then you're a revenant!
好的
all right.
如果我是两者之一 我还会拿银匕首这样做吗
If I was either, would I do this with a silver knife?
真的是迪恩
Dean?
这就是我要向你证明的事实
That's what I've been trying to tell you.
小子 见到你真好
It's…it's good to see you, boy.
是的 我也是
Yeah, you too.
但是
But…
你是怎么逃出来的
How did you bust out?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我只是
I just, uh…
醒来时发现自己置身于一片松海之中
just woke up in a pine bo…
我也不是恶魔
I'm not a demon, either, you know.
抱歉
Sorry.
万事小心为妙
can't be too careful.
这一点都说不通啊
That don't make a lick of sense.
对 你以为在向唱诗班说教吗
Yeah. yeah, you're preaching to the choir.
迪恩 四个月前你可是胸口被撕裂
Dean, your chest was ribbons, your insides were slop,
内脏外泻着下葬的
and you'd been buried four months.
即使你能逃出地狱回到你的肉身里
even if you could slip out of hell and back into your meats …
我明白了 我应该看起来像恐怖MV里的鬼怪
I know. I should look like a "thriller" video reject.
你还记得什么
What do you remember?
不多
not much.
我记得自己成了地狱之犬的磨牙玩具
I remember I was a hellhound's chew toy…
然后眼前一片昏暗
and then lights-out.
我就在地下6英尺处了 就这些了
Then I come to six feet under.that was it.
萨姆的电话打不通
Sam's number's not working.
他 他不会也
He's, uh … he's not…
就我所知 他还活着
Oh, he's alive, as far as I know.
太好了
good.
等等 什么叫就你所知
Wait. what do you mean …as far as you know?
我几个月没联系他了
I haven't talked to him for months.
你开什么玩笑 你就这么让他一个人离开了
You're kidding? you just let him go off by himself?
他铁了心要这样
He was dead set on it.
鲍比你应该照看好他的
Bobby, you should have been looking after him.
我尽力了
I tried.
这几个月对我或者对他来说
These last months haven't been exactly easy,
都是痛苦难熬的日子
You know, for him or me.
我们不得不亲手埋葬你
We had to bury you.
你们为什么要土葬我
Why did you bury me, anyway?
我本打算撒了盐一把火烧了你 一贯做法
I wanted you salted and burned … usual drill.
萨姆却不想这样
But sam wouldn't have it.
我很高兴他做了明智的决定
Well, I'm glad he won that one.
他说召唤你回来时你会需要一个躯壳
He said you'd need a body when he gotou back home somehow.
- 他就说了这些 - 你什么意思
- That's about all he said. - What do you mean?
他很平静
He was quiet…
太过平静
real quiet.
然后就这么离开了 再也没回过我电话
Then he just took off.wouldn't return my calls.
我试着找他 但他却躲着我
I tried to find him, but he don't want to be found.
该死的 萨姆
Oh, damn it, sammy.
怎么了
What?
他把我召唤回来了
Oh, he got me home okay.
一定是用了黑巫术才办到的
But whatever he did, it is bad mojo.
你为何如此肯定 你该看看坟墓的位置
What makes you so sure?you should have seen the grave site.
就像是核爆
It was like a nuke went off.
然后有一股力量 感觉是鬼怪
Then there was this …this force, this presence,
我不确定
That, i don't know,
但它吹过了我 使破碎的关节都粘合了
But it … it … it blew past me at a fill-up joint.
然后就有这个了
and then this.
这是什么鬼东西
What in the hell?
就像一个恶魔把我拉了出来或吊了起来
Yeah, it's like a demon just yanked me out or rode me out.
但是为什么呢
But why?
履行他们的契约
To hold up their end of the bargain.
你认为萨姆签了份契约
You think sam made a deal?
是我也会这么做的
It's what I would have done.
你好
Yeah, hi.
我向你们买过一部手机
I have a, uh, cellphone account with you guys.
但是丢了
and, uh, lost my phone.
你们能否为我开下GPS定位系统
I was wondering if you could turn the gps on for me.
名字是温迪·安特列斯
Yeah. the name's "wedge antilles."
社保号是2474
Social is 2474.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么知道他用了这个名字
How'd you know he'd use that name?
我好比他肚子里的蛔虫
You kidding me? what don't I know about that kid?
鲍比
Hey, bobby.
这儿怎么成酒吧了
What's the deal with the liquor store, hmm?
你朋友出城了还是其他什么
Your parents out of town or something?
就像我刚说的
like I said,
过去的几个月是多么的痛苦难熬
The last few months ain't been all that easy.
的确
right.
萨姆在伊利诺斯州的庞蒂亚克城
Sam's in pontiac, illinois.
离你被埋的地方很近
right near where you were planted.
就在我现世的地方
right where I popped up.
你觉得真是巧合吗
Hell of a coincidence, don't you think?
东西呢
So, where is it?
什么
Where's what?
要两个人来送的披萨
The pizza that takes two guys to deliver.
我想我们走错房间了
I think we got the wrong room.
怎么了
Hey, is …
好啊 萨姆
Hey, ya, sammy.
你是谁
Who are you?!
别搞得你没做过似的 我做了什么
like you didn't do this!do what?!
是他 是他 萨姆
It's him.it's him, sam.
我已经验证过了 的确是他
I've been through this already.it's really him.
但是
But…
我明白
I know.
我看上去像幻觉是吧
I look fantastic, huh?
你们俩在搞基？
So, are you two, like…together?
什么 不对
What? no.
不是
no.
他是我哥哥
He's my brother.
我想我明白了
got it…i-i guess.
也许我该走了
look, i should probably go.
对 对 这不失为一个好主意 失陪
Yeah, yeah. that's probably a good idea. sorry.
记得打电话给我
So, call me.
好的 当然会的 凯茜
Yeah, yeah.surehing, kathy.
克利斯蒂
christie.
对
right.
告诉我复活我的代价是什么
So, tell me, what'd it cost?
那女孩
The girl?
一点都不好笑 萨姆
That's not funny, sam.
把我救回来
To bring me back.
代价是什么
What'd it cost?
出卖你的灵魂还是更糟的什么
Was it just your soul, or was it something worse?
- 你认为我和恶魔签了契约 - 我们都是这么想的
- You think I made a deal? - That's exactly what we think.
我没有啊
Well, i didn't.
别骗我
Don't lie to me.
我没骗你
I'm not lying.
现在这样你满意吗
So, what now?
我解脱了 你却被控制了 不是吗
I'm off the hook, and you're on, is that it?
你是不是鬼迷心窍了
You're some demon's bitch boy?
我不愿意这样被你救活
I didn't want to be saved like this.
迪恩 我本打算能这么做的
look, dean, i wish I had done it, all right?
这事绝对不会这么结束的
There's no other way that this could have gone down.
现在告诉我真相
now tell the truth!
我试遍了救你的路子 这就是真相
I tried everything. that's the truth.
我试图敲开地狱之门
I tried opening the devil's gate.
我试图去交易 迪恩
Hell, i tried to bargain, dean,
但没一个恶魔愿意交易
But no demon would deal, all right?
你在地狱里煎熬了好几个月 好几个月
You were rotting in hell for months … for months.
但我却阻止不了
and I couldn't stop it.
很遗憾不是我救你的 行了吧
So, I'm sorry it wasn't me, all right?
迪恩 对不起
Dean, I'm sorry.
没关系 萨姆
It's okay, sammy.
你不用道歉 我相信你
You don't have to apologize. I believe you.
别高兴太早
Don't get me wrong …
我很高兴萨姆的灵魂还完整
I am gladdened that sam's soul remains intact,
但更恐怖的问题出来了
But that does raise a sticky question.
如果不是你救我出来 那到底是谁
If he didn't pull me out, then what did?
如果不是你挖我出坟墓的
Are you doing around here…
那你怎么在这一带转悠
if you weren't digging me out of my grave?
当我知道自己不能救你以后
Well, once I figured out I couldn't save you,
我就开始抓捕莉莉丝
um…i started hunting down lilith,
希望能作些补偿
Trying to get some payback.
你自己去抓吗
all by yourself?
你以为你是谁 你老爸？
Who do you think you are, your old man?
是的 抱歉 鲍比
Yeah, I'm sorry, bobby.
我应该先打给你 我搞砸了一切
I-i should have called. I was pretty messed up.
没错 我很能体会你的心情
Oh, yeah. I really feel your pain.
不过 我正在找离开田纳西州的魔鬼们
anyways, uh, i was checking these demons out of tennessee,
他们走得很急 都事先到这里了
and out of nowhere they took a hard left, booked up here.
- 什么时候 - 昨天早上
- When? - Yesterday morning.
我出来的时候
When I busted out.
你认为这些鬼怪是因为你才来这里的
You think these demons are here cause of you?
但是为什么呢
But why?
我不知道
Well, i don't know.
某些烂鬼把我拖出坟墓 现在又来这一套
Some badass demon drags me out, and now this?
肯定有某种联系
It's got to be connected somehow.
你现在感觉怎么样
How you feeling, anyway?
我有点饿
I'm a little hungry.
不 我的意思是 你觉得你还象自己吗
no, i mean, do you feel like yourself?
- 有奇怪的事吗 不同的事 - 有魔力了吗？
- Anything strange or different? - Or demonic?
鲍比 我得象你证明多少次 我就是我
Bobby, how many times do I have to prove I'm me?
听着 没有哪个魔鬼会对你
Yeah, well, listen … no demon's letting you loose.
大发慈悲之心的
Out of the goodness of their hearts.
他们早就做好了肮脏的计划了
They got to have something nasty planned.
- 我觉得很好 - 好了 我们不知道他们计划了什么
- well, I feel fine. - Okay, look, we don't know what they're planning.
我们有一堆问题没法解决
We got a pile of questions and no shovel.
得寻求帮助
We need help.
我认识位通灵师 离这里几个小时车程
I know a psychic a few hours from here.
象这样大的事情 她应该多少有点消息
Something this big, maybe she's heard the other side talking.
好 值得一试 我快去快回
Hell, yeah. it's worth a shot. I'll be right back.
等下
Hey, wait.
你得拿回这个
You probably want this back.
谢谢
Thanks.
别客气
Don't mention it.
迪恩 那里怎么样
Hey, dean, what was it like?
哪里 地狱吗
What? hell?
我不知道 我两眼一抹黑
I don't know. i-i-i-i must have blacked it out.
什么都记不得了
I don't remember a damn thing.
那样最好
Thank god for that.
是的
Yeah.
她在州际公路边 离这里大概四小时
She's about four hours down the interstate.
别跟丢了
Try to keep up.
我肯定你很想开车
I assume you'll want to drive.
我都快忘了
I almost forgot.
宝贝 想我了吗
Hey, sweetheart, did you miss me?
- 那是什么 - 那是ipod的固定插座
- What the hell is that? - That's an ipod jack.
你应该好好照顾我的车 别给她打孔
You were supposed to take care of her, not douche her up.
迪恩 我本以为这车归我了
Dean, i thought it was my car.
你玩真的了
really?
还有件事我不明白
There still one thing that's bothering me.
什么
Yeah?
我咬了 或者是被咬的那晚
Yeah. the night that I bit it … or got bit.
你怎么逃出来的 我以为莉莉丝会杀了你
How'd you make it out? I thought lilith was gonna kill you.
她是想的 可是她没有
Well, she tried. she couldn't.
她没有 是什么意思
What do you mean she couldn't?
她点火了 就在我面前想烧死我
She fired this, like, burning light at me,
但是 我一道疤都没留下
and… it didn't leave a scratch,
就好象我是免疫的 或者别的什么原因
like I was immune or something.
免疫
Immune?
对
Yeah.
我不知道我们谁更惊讶 她还是我
I don't know who was more surprised … her or me.
之后她跑得无影无踪了
She left pretty fast after that.
露比呢 她到哪里去了
What about ruby? where is she?
死了 下地狱了
Dead or in hell.
看来你飘忽不定的超能力又有反映了？
So, you been using your, uh, freaky e.s.p. stuff?
不是
no.
你肯定？
Sure about that?
我是说 现在你得到了免疫性
ah, well, i mean, now that you got immunity …
不管这到底是什么 我只是想知道
Whatever the hell that is … just wondering.
你还会发生哪些古怪的事情
What other kind of weirdo crap you got going on.
没了 迪恩
nothing, dean.
你不让我在这条路上继续走下去
look, you didn't want me to go down that road,
我就没有继续走下去
So I didn't go down that road.
这还不是你的临终遗言吗
It was practically your dying wish.
好 我们都一起保留着吧
Yeah, well, let's keep it that way.
鲍比
Bobby!
你太迷人了
You're a sight for sore eyes.
就是这俩男孩吗
So, are these the boys?
萨姆 迪恩 这是帕梅拉·巴恩斯
Sam, dean … pamela barnes.
这个州里最好的通灵师
Best damn psychic in the state.
你好
Hey. hi.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean winchester.
才下火山 又进油锅啊
Out of the fire and back in the frying pan, huh?
一个独一无二的迪恩
Makes you a rare individual.
你说的对
If you say so.
进来吧
come on in.
你有没有听到什么风声？
So, you hear anything?
我通过一打灵魂来进行占卜
Well, i ouija-ed my way through a dozen spirits.
没一个知道谁救了迪恩并且为什么
no one seems to know who broke your boy out or why.
- 下一步干嘛？- 问的好
- So, what's next? - As nice, I think.
看看谁动了这契约
See if we can see who did the deed.
你不会是想在这儿召唤恶魔吧
You're not gonna summon the damn thing here?
当然不是
no.
我只是想偷看一眼
I just want to get a sneak peek at it,
就像没有水晶的水晶球
like a crystal ball without the crystal.
我去试试
I'm game.
杰西是谁？
Who's jesse?
这不重要了
Well, it wasn't forever.
他死了
His loss.
你有机会了哦
Might be your gain.
伙计 听起来真爽
Dude, I'm so in.
是啊 她会缠着你度过余生
Yeah, she's gonna eat you alive.
是啊 不过我会逃离这一切的 等着吧
Hey, i just got out of jail.bring it.
你也一起吧
You're invited, too, grumpy.
这事你别搅合
You are not invited.
互相牵着手
Take each other's hands.
我将接触一个神秘怪物也接触过的东西
And I need to touch something our mystery monster touched.
可别在这儿碰我
Whoa! well, he didn't touch me there.
我的错
My mistake.
我召唤并命令你
I invoke, conjure and command you.
出现在我面前
appear unto me before this circle.
我召唤并命令你
I invoke, conjure, and command you.
出现在我面前
appear unto me before this circle.
我召唤并命令你
I invoke, conjure, and command you.
出现在我面前
appear unto me before this circle.
我召唤…
I invoke…
卡西迪奥？
castiello?
不 对不起 卡西迪奥 我并不感到恐慌
no. sorry, castiello, i don't scare easy.
卡西迪奥？-是个人名
castiello? its name.
它在我耳边警告我别管这事
It's whispering to me, warning me to turn back.
我召唤并命令你显出你的真面目吧
I conjure and command you show me your face.
我召唤并命令你 - 也许我们该停下来
I conjure and command you. maybe we should stop.
我快搞定了
I almost got it.
我命令你显出你的真面目吧
I command you show me your face.
现身吧
Show me your face now!
我看不见了
I can't see.
I can't see!
上帝啊 不
Oh, god, no.
听你的
Yeah, you bet.
鲍比怎么说？
What'd bobby say?
帕梅出重症监护室了 病情稳定
uh, pam's stable and out of icu.
因为我们她失明了？
and blind 'cause of us?
现在我们还是没有任何线索
and we still have no clue what we're dealing with.
那还不是完整的事实？-不
That's not entirely true.no?
知道那个叫卡西迪奥的家伙
We got a name castiello or whatever.
有着巨大的身形 我们可以召唤它 让他告诉我们
With the right mumbo jumbo we could summon him, bring him right to us.
你疯了 绝对不行
You're crazy.absolutely not.
我的意思是在它干了些什么之后 我们会干掉它
We'll work him over.i mean, after what he did?
帕梅就偷看了一眼 她的眼睛就没了
pam took a peek at him and her eyes burned out of her skull,
你还想和他面对面？
and you want to have a face-to-face?
你有好注意了？-目前看 是的
You got a better idea?yeah, as a matter of fact, i do.
我跟着一些恶魔来到镇里了 - 不错
I followed some demons to town, right?okay?
去找到他们
So we go find them.
它们肯定知道些什么
Someone's got to know something about something.
谢谢
Thanks.
你在等小费么？
You angling for a tip?
对不起 我觉得你们是在找我们
I'm sorry. I thought you were looking for us.
迪恩…
Dean…
在地狱兜了一圈回来了
To hell and back.
你是不是太走运了？
aren't you a lucky duck?
那就是我
That's me.
你觉得已经摆脱困境了？
So, you get to just stroll out of the pit, huh?
告诉我 是什么让你如此特别？
Tell me, what makes you so special?
可能是因为我长的太帅了
I like to think it's because of my perky nipples.
我也不知道
I don't know.
不是我干的 也不知道是谁帮了我
It wasn't my doing.i don't know who pulled me out.
好吧 不是你
right.you don't.
对 不是我
no, i don't.
撒谎是罪孽
lying's a sin, you know.
我没骗你
I'm not lying.
不过我很乐意查明真相
But I'd like to find out.
如果你不乐意开导我的话
So if you wouldn't mind enlightening me, flo.
注意你的口气 伙计
Mind your tone with me, boy.
我可以亲自把你送回地狱
I'll drag you back to hell myself.
你不会的
no, you won't.
不会？-不
no?no.
如果你会你早就下手了
cause if you were, you'd have done it already.
情况是你也不知道谁救了我
The fact is, you don't know who cut me loose.
还有看来你们也在查这事
and you're just as spooked as we are.
也在寻找答案
and you're looking for answers.
难道是超能力的鬼魂？
Well, maybe it was some turbocharged spirit, hmm?
哥斯拉？
Or, uh, godzilla.
或者是什么终极魔鬼
Or some big, bad boss demon.
不过我猜应该很厉害
But I'm guessing at your pay grade.
他们没告诉你
That they don't tell you squat.
不管它是谁
cause whoever it was,
他们要我离开那里…
They want me out…
他们肯定强过你们
and they're a lot stronger than you.
来吧 把我送回去
So, go ahead.send me back.
不过别爬着来见我
But don't come crawling to me.
他们会用灭火水龙头和凡士林照顾你
When they show up on your front doorstep.
当你跨入门的一霎那
With some vaseline and a fire hose.
我会割断你的喉咙 再把你的肺拿出来
I'm gonna reach down your throat and rip out your lungs.
我也这么想的
That's what I thought.
我们走 萨姆
let's go, sam.
派的钱
for the pie.
真他妈的好险啊
Holy crap, that was close.
我们差点没能从里面逃出来 迪恩
We're not just gonna leave them in there, are we, dean?
不错 他们有三个 可能更多
Well, yeah. there's three of them, probably more.
我们只有两个人加一把匕首
We only got one knife between us.
最近我已经干掉很多恶魔了
I've been killing a lot more demons than that lately.
不再是了 你高明的兄弟回来了
not anymore. the smarter brother's back in town.
迪恩 我们得干掉它们 它们很危险
Dean, we got to take them. they are dangerous.
它们也很害怕 好吧？
They're scared, okay?
它们在害怕把我从里面拉出来的那个家伙
Scared of whatever had the juice to yank me out.
我们在处理一个大问题
We're dealing with a bad mofo here. one job at a time.
迪恩
Dean!
你怎么样了 孩子
How you doing, kid?
就是脑子里还有些教堂的钟响
aside from the church bells ringing in my head…
有点晕
peachy.
你干吗呢
Hey. what are you doing?
睡不着 想吃汉堡
couldn't sleep. went to get a burger.
- 在我的车里 - 习惯了 抱歉 你干吗呢
- In my car? force of habit, sorry. - What are you doing up?
鲍比回来了 我们去喝一杯啤酒
Well, uh, bobby's back. we're going to grab a beer.
好的 把我那份也喝了
all right. well, uh, spill some for me, huh?
没问题 待会我找你
Done. yeah, I'll catch you later.
你干嘛不告诉他
Why the hell didn't you tell him?
因为他要阻止我们
cause he'd just try to stop us.
阻止什么 召唤那个东西
from what? summoning this thing.
现在是正面争锋相对的时候了
It's time we face it head on.
- 你不是来真的吧 - 怎么不是
- You can't be serious. - As a heart attack.
正是时候呢
It's high noon, baby.
我们根本不知道它是什么东西
We don't know what it is.
可能是恶魔 也可能是任何什么东西
I-it could be a demon. it could be anything.
这就是为什么我们要做好一切的准备
That's why we got to be ready for anything.
我们有把一流的魔法匕首
We got the big-time magic knife.
你车厢里根本就有个军火库
You got an arsenal in the trunk.
这个主意可不好
This is a bad idea.
严重同意 不过我们还有什么其它选择
I couldn't agree more, but what other choice do we have?
我们可以选择生命
We could choose life.
鲍比 不管这个是什么 不管它想要什么
Bobby, whatever this is, whatever it wants,
它是冲我来的 我们都知道这个 对吧
It's after me … that much we know, right?
我根本就无处躲藏
Well, i got no place to hide.
我要么被它干掉
I can either get caught with my pants down again,
要么是我们干掉它
Or we can make our stand.
迪恩 萨姆这次可以帮忙的
Dean, we could use sam for this.
他在那会比较好
nah, he's better off where he is.
你的眼睛
Your eyes.
你的灵魂在一英里远我都能闻到
I could still smell your soul a mile away.
谁来过 你看到了的
Who was here? you saw it.
我看到了
I saw it.
是什么
What was it?
一切都结束了
It's the end.
我们死了 我们都死了
We're dead. we're all dead.
你看到什么了
What did you see?
去死吧
go to hell.
真有意思
funny…
我正准备跟你说同样的话
I was gonna say the same thing to you.
该死
Damn it.
干的漂亮嘛 萨姆 你总是越来越棒
getting pretty slick there, sam. better all the time.
这些都是什么鬼东西 露比
What the hell's going on around here, ruby?
我也想知道
I wish I knew.
我们在想可能是某些高等级的恶魔离开了迪恩
We were thinking some high-level demon pulled dean out.
不可能
no way.
萨姆 人类的灵魂不会直接就离开地狱
Sam, human souls don't just walk out of hell.
然后轻易的就进入他们的身体
and back into their bodies easy.
这家伙滴血 大地也颤抖
This guy bleeds, the ground quakes …
这些都是正常的
It's cosmic.
没有恶魔可以撼动这个
no demon can swing that.
莉莉丝也不行
not lilith…
任何人都不行
not anybody.
那什么可以
Then what can?
我从来没见过的
nothing I've ever seen before.
这真是一件艺术品啊
That's a hell of an art project you got going there.
陷阱和护身符是世界通用的
Traps and talismans from every faith on the globe.
干得怎样了？
How you doing?
木桩 铁器 银器 圣盐 匕首
Stakes, iron, silver, salt, a knife.
我想 我们差不多准备好了
I mean, we're pretty much set.
足以对付以往见过的任何东西
To catch and kill anything I've ever heard of.
这依旧不是个好主意
This is still a bad idea.
鲍比 以前你从没说过这种话
Yeah, bobby, i heard you the first 10 times.
现在就开始吧 怎么样？
What do you say we ring the dinner bell?
您还真是金口难开
So, million-dollar question …
打算把我们做的事情告诉你哥哥吗
You gonna tell dean about what we're doing?
当然 只是在寻找合适的时机
Yeah, i just got to figure out the right way to say it.
只是需要点时间 仅此而已
look, i just need time, okay? that's all.
萨姆 他会发现的
Sam, he's gonna find out,
如果你不亲自告诉他 他会被气死
and if it's not from you, he's gonna be pissed.
不管怎样 他都会被气死
Oh, he's gonna be pissed anyway.
对于通灵 他一向顽固
He's so hardheaded about this psychic stuff,
到时候他一定会阻止我
He'll just try and stop me.
我还是先暂时低调一点
Look, maybe I'll just take a step back for a while.
露比
Ruby.
说实话 我不是很喜欢你哥哥
I mean, I'm not exactly in your brother's fan club,
但他是你兄弟 我不想插手你们的事情
But he is your brother, and I'm not gonna come between you.
露比 听着
ruby, listen.
我不知道我这样做是否正确
I don't know if what I'm doing is right.
甚至都不知道 是不是信任你
Hell, i don't even know if I trust you.
多谢直言相告
Thanks.
但是我知道自己在救助大众
What I do know is I'm saving people…
和阻止魔鬼
and stopping demons.
这感觉很好
and that feels good.
我想继续下去
I want to keep going.
你确定仪式没出错？
You sure you did the ritual right?
不好意思
Sorry.
真是麻烦
Touchy, touchy, huh?
往好处想 这说不定只是阵风而已
Wishful thinking, but maybe it's just the wind.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我就是那个紧紧抓着你
I'm the one who gripped you tight.
带你离开地狱的人
and raised you from perdition.
感激不尽
Thanks for that.
我们要谈谈 迪恩
We need to talk, dean.
单独谈
alone.
你朋友还活着
Your friend is alive.
你是谁
Who are you?
卡西迪奥
castiello.
我猜也是 我的意思是 你是什么东西
Yeah, i figured that much. I mean what are you?
我是侍奉主的天使
I'm an angel of the lord.
得了吧
get the hell out of here.
根本就没有这种东西
There's no such thing.
这就是你的症结所在
This is your problem, dean.
你没有信仰
You have no faith.
就算你是天使吧
Some angel you are.
你把那可怜女人的眼睛烧伤了
You burned out that poor woman's eyes.
我警告过她不要尝试窥探我的真面目
I warned her not to spy on my true form.
对人类来说 他们无法承受
It can be overwhelming to humans.
他们也无法承受我的真实声音
and so can my real voice…
当然你体验过了
But you already knew that.
在加油站和汽车旅馆里面？
You mean the gas station and the motel?
那是你在说话？
That was you talking?
伙计 下次要降低音调
Buddy, next time, lower the volume.
是我的不是
That was my mistake.
有些人 特别的人
Certain people, special people.
能感知到我的面容
can perceive my true visage.
我以为你会是其中之一
I thought you would be one of them.
我想错了
I was wrong.
那你现在的容貌是？
and what visage are you in now, huh?
难道是 圣职税务会计？
What … holy tax accountant?
这个？是具皮囊而已
This? this is…a vessel.
你占据了某个混蛋的身体？
You're possessing some poor bastard?
他是个虔诚的信徒 这是他祈求而来的
He's a devout man. he actually prayed for this.
伙计 我可不吃你这套
look, pal, I'm not buying what you're selling.
说真的 你到底是谁
So who are you, really?
已经告知你了
I told you.
好吧
right.
那为什么一个天使要救我出地狱？
and why would an angel rescue me from hell?
好运会降临的 迪恩
good things do happen, dean.
从来没降临到我的头上
not in my experience.
到底怎么了
What's the matter?
难道你不认为自己应当被救赎？
You don't think you deserve to be saved.
那你为什么这么做
Why'd you do it?
因为这是天主下的命令
Because god commanded it.
因为我们有任务交给你
Because we have work for you.